{
  "datas": [
    {
      "question": "The capital of Azerbaijan ?",
      "answers": ["", "Baku", "Sheki", "Ganja", "Kalbacar"],
      "correctAns": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which one is Fruit?",
      "answers": ["", "Cucumber", "Tomato", "Kiwi", "Rose"],
      "correctAns": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Mark Zuckerberg owns?",
      "answers": ["", "Amazon", "Meta", "Apple", "Google"],
      "correctAns": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Year of neither Messi nor Ronaldo won the Ballon d'Or ?",
      "answers": ["", "2012", "2013", "2018", "2021"],
      "correctAns": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Turkish Rapper ?",
      "answers": ["", "Eminem", "Tupac", "Khose", "Ezhel"],
      "correctAns": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the currency of Azerbaijan? ?",
      "answers": ["", "Manat ðŸ’´", "Rub ðŸ’µ", "Euro ðŸ’¶", "USD ðŸ’²"],
      "correctAns": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How many colors are there in a rainbow?",
      "answers": ["", "5", "7", "3", "12"],
      "correctAns": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Painter of MonaLisa Portret ?",
      "answers": [
        "",
        "Leonardo da Vinci",
        "Vincent van Gogh",
        "Michelangelo",
        "Salvador DalÃ­"
      ],
      "correctAns": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which doesn't include NeighbourCountry?",
      "answers": ["", "Japan", "Germany", "Poland", "Czech"],
      "correctAns": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is impossible ?",
      "answers": ["", "26/09/2022", "31/04/2017", "28/02/2014", "30/08/2016"],
      "correctAns": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Eiffel Tower places in ?",
      "answers": ["", "Paris", "Viana", "Berlin", "Madrid"],
      "correctAns": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The biggest Country ?",
      "answers": ["", "USA", "CANADA", "RUSSIA", "BRASIL"],
      "correctAns": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "The highest top of Mountain ?",
      "answers": ["", "Kangchenjunga", "Lhotse", "Everest", "Makalu"],
      "correctAns": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Type of Modern Human ?",
      "answers": [
        "",
        "Homo Sapiens",
        "Neanderthalensis",
        "Homo Erectus",
        "Homo floresiensis"
      ],
      "correctAns": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the highest-rated film on IMDb?",
      "answers": [
        "",
        "God Father",
        "Shaswank redemption",
        "Forest Gump",
        "Green Mile"
      ],
      "correctAns": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which one is not olmypics race?",
      "answers": ["", "Kickboxing", "Boxing", "Swimming", "Judo"],
      "correctAns": 1
    }
  ]
}
